#### John Gee

678-294-9064 johngee3@icloud.com 2180 Parliament Drive Lawrenceville, GA 30043

## **Profile**

Customer service representative focused on providing reliable, fast, and efficient support to customers. Able to quickly learn POS and other computer systems in order to do so. 4 years experience in customer service industry, driven to provide the best customer experience.

## Education

Georgia Southern University, Statesboro, GA – BS Information Technology, 2012-Present

#### Skills

- HTML/CSS
- Microsoft Office Suite
- Adobe Creative Suite
- POS Systems

# Experience

ASSISTANT DEPARTMENT HEAD, GRAYS COLLEGE BOOKSTORE - 2013 - 2015

- Provided customer service.
- Kept the store neat and organized, performed opening and closing duties.
- Received and shipped book shipments and updated inventory respectively.

PRODUCTION STAFF, MISTER CARWASH - 2016 - 2017

- Maintained the grounds of carwash.
- Managed on-site logistics by monitoring real time traffic flows.
- Provided customer service.